[ti:长难句11~20]
[ar:sunny]
[al:]
[by:sunny]
[00:00.00]11. Such variations 
[00:02.31]in size, shape, chemistry, 
[00:04.59]conduction speed, excitation 
[00:06.75]threshold, and the like 
[00:08.12]as had been demonstrated 
[00:09.48]in nerve cells remained 
[00:10.78]negligible in significance 
[00:12.32]for any possible correlation 
[00:13.85]with the manifold dimensions 
[00:15.31]of mental experience. 
[00:17.25]12. It was possible 
[00:19.26]to demonstrate by other 
[00:20.50]methods refined structural 
[00:21.93]differences among neuron 
[00:23.18]types; however, proof 
[00:25.43]was lacking that the 
[00:26.32]quality of the impulse 
[00:27.48]or its condition was 
[00:28.53]influenced by these 
[00:29.51]differences, which seemed 
[00:30.90]instead to influence 
[00:31.92]the developmental patterning 
[00:33.40]of the neural circuits.  
[00:35.31]13. Although qualitative 
[00:38.00]variance among nerve 
[00:39.04]energies was never rigidly 
[00:40.53]disproved, the doctrine 
[00:42.07]was generally abandoned 
[00:43.32]in favor of the opposing 
[00:44.53]view, namely, that nerve 
[00:46.26]impulses are essentially 
[00:47.46]homogeneous in quality 
[00:48.90]and are transmitted 
[00:49.85]as "common currency" 
[00:51.06]throughout the nervous 
[00:51.84]system. 14. Other experiments 
[00:55.32]revealed slight variations 
[00:56.73]in the size, number, 
[00:58.32]arrangement, and interconnection 
[01:00.03]of the nerve cells, 
[01:01.26]but as far as psycho 
[01:02.56]neural correlations 
[01:03.56]were concerned, the 
[01:04.70]obvious similarities 
[01:05.90]of these sensory fields 
[01:07.20]to each other seemed 
[01:08.09]much more remarkable 
[01:09.29]than any of the minute 
[01:10.23]differences. 15. Although 
[01:13.43]some experiments show 
[01:14.78]that, as an object becomes 
[01:16.37]familiar, its internal 
[01:17.90]representation becomes 
[01:19.10]more holistic and the 
[01:20.14]recognition process 
[01:21.31]correspondingly more 
[01:22.50]parallel, the weight 
[01:23.78]of evidence seems to 
[01:24.89]support the serial hypothesis, 
[01:27.03]at least for objects 
[01:28.28]that are not notably 
[01:29.23]simple and familiar. 
[01:31.01]16. In large part as 
[01:33.40]a consequence of　the 
[01:34.40]feminist movement, historians 
[01:36.29]have focused a great 
[01:37.45]deal of attention in 
[01:38.39]recent years on determining 
[01:39.73]more accurately the 
[01:40.64]status of women in various 
[01:42.23]periods.  17. If one 
[01:45.43]begins by examining 
[01:46.67]why ancients refer to 
[01:48.07]Amazons, it becomes 
[01:49.51]clear that ancient Greek 
[01:50.76]descriptions of such 
[01:51.85]societies were meant 
[01:53.00]not so much to represent 
[01:54.50]observed historical 
[01:55.54]fact - real amazonian 
[01:57.04]societies - but rather 
[01:58.57]to offer “moral lessons” 
[01:59.98]on the supposed outcome 
[02:01.39]of women’s rule in their 
[02:02.56]own society. 18. Thus, 
[02:06.10]for instance, it may 
[02:07.46]come as a shock to mathematicians 
[02:09.29]to learn that the schrodinger 
[02:10.40]equation for the hydrogen 
[02:11.73]atom is not a literally 
[02:12.89]correct description 
[02:13.79]of this atom, but only 
[02:15.23]an approximation to 
[02:16.48]a somewhat more correct 
[02:17.48]equation taking account 
[02:18.85]of spin, magnetic dipole, 
[02:21.03]and relativistic effects; 
[02:23.25]and that this corrected　
[02:24.29]equation is itself only 
[02:25.84]an imperfect approximation 
[02:27.48]to an infinite set of　
[02:28.53]quantum field-theoretical 
[02:29.93]equations. 19. The physicist 
[02:33.42]rightly dreads precise 
[02:34.62]argument, since an argument 
[02:36.42]that is　convincing only 
[02:37.76]if it is precise loses 
[02:39.10]all its force if the 
[02:40.29]assumptions on　which 
[02:41.34]it is based are slightly 
[02:42.64]changed, whereas an 
[02:43.93]argument that is convincing 
[02:45.43]though imprecise may 
[02:46.43]well be stable under 
[02:47.57]small perturbations 
[02:48.78]of its underlying assumptions. 
[02:51.01]20. However, as they 
[02:53.26]gained cohesion, the 
[02:54.60]bluestockings came to 
[02:55.81]regard themselves as 
[02:57.09]a women's group and 
[02:57.93]to possess a sense of 
[02:58.93]female solidarity lacking 
[03:00.43]in the salonnieres, 
[03:01.89]who remained isolated 
[03:03.12]from one another by 
[03:03.98]the primacy each held 
[03:05.32]in her own salon. 
