[ti:长难句41~50]
[ar:sunny]
[al:]
[by:sunny]
[00:00.00]71. Open acknowledgement 
[00:02.81]of the existence of 
[00:03.87]women’s oppression was 
[00:05.01]too radical for the 
[00:06.01]united stated in the 
[00:07.12]fifties, and beauvoir’s 
[00:08.67]conclusion , that change 
[00:10.21]in women’s economic 
[00:11.26]condition, though insufficient 
[00:12.87]by itself, “remains 
[00:14.32]the basic factor ” in 
[00:15.42]improving women’s situation , 
[00:17.14]was particularly unacceptable . 
[00:19.68]72. Other theorists 
[00:22.03]propose that the moon 
[00:22.98]was ripped out of the 
[00:23.84]earth’s rocky mantle 
[00:25.09]by the earth’s collision 
[00:26.18]with another large celestial 
[00:27.64]body after much of the 
[00:28.73]earth’s iron fell to 
[00:30.00]its core.  73. However, 
[00:33.64]recent scholarship has 
[00:34.93]strongly suggested that 
[00:36.25]those aspects of early 
[00:37.59]New England culture 
[00:38.56]that seem to have been 
[00:39.36]most distinctly puritan, 
[00:41.00]such as the strong religious 
[00:42.40]orientation and the 
[00:43.43]communal impulse, were 
[00:44.89]not even typical of 
[00:46.15]New England as a whole, 
[00:47.50]but were largely confined 
[00:48.86]to the two colonies 
[00:49.86]of Massachusetts and 
[00:50.96]Connecticut.  74. Thus, 
[00:54.36]what in contrast to 
[00:55.45]the puritan colonies 
[00:56.61]appears to davis to 
[00:57.61]be peculiarly southern -  
[00:59.17]acquisitiveness, a strong 
[01:00.87]interest in politics 
[01:02.07]and the law, and　a tendency 
[01:03.71]to cultivate metropolitan　
[01:05.26]cultural models - was 
[01:06.76]not only more typically 
[01:08.21]english than the cultural 
[01:09.36]patterns exhibited by 
[01:10.57]puritan massachusetts 
[01:12.03]and connecticut, but 
[01:13.18]also almost certainly 
[01:14.62]characteristic　of most 
[01:15.78]other early modern british　
[01:17.17]colonies from barbados 
[01:18.78]north to rhode island 
[01:20.07]and new hampshire. 75. 
[01:23.34]Portrayals of the folk 
[01:24.59]of Mecklenburg County, 
[01:25.98]North Carolina, whom 
[01:27.23]he remembers from early 
[01:28.43]childhood, of the jazz 
[01:29.98]musicians and tenement 
[01:31.29]roofs of his Harlem 
[01:32.32]days, of Pittsburgh 
[01:33.70]steelworkers, and his 
[01:35.04]reconstruction of classical 
[01:36.50]Greek myths in the guise 
[01:37.65]of the ancient black 
[01:38.75]kingdom of Benin, attest 
[01:40.25]to this. 76. A very 
[01:43.64]specialized feeding 
[01:44.86]adaptation in zooplankton 
[01:46.50]is that of the tadpolelike 
[01:47.76]appendicularian who 
[01:49.00]lives in a walnut-sized （
[01:50.51]or smaller） balloon 
[01:51.56]of mucus equipped with 
[01:52.76]filters that　capture 
[01:53.75]and concentrate phytoplankton.  
[01:56.15]77. These historians, 
[01:59.01]however, have analyzed 
[02:00.51]less fully the development 
[02:01.76]of specifically feminist 
[02:03.21]ideas and　activities 
[02:04.51]during the same period. 
[02:06.31]78. Apparently most 
[02:08.87]massive stars manage 
[02:10.18]to lose sufficient material 
[02:11.62]that their masses drop 
[02:12.67]below the critical value 
[02:13.93]of 1.4 m before they 
[02:15.71]exhaust their nuclear 
[02:16.87]fuel.  79. This is so 
[02:20.23]even though armed forces 
[02:21.59]operate in an ethos 
[02:22.89]of institutional change 
[02:24.23]oriented toward occupational 
[02:25.73]equality and under the 
[02:26.89]federal sanction of 
[02:27.93]equal pay for equal 
[02:29.03]work. 80. An impact (
[02:31.84]on the mars) capable 
[02:32.93]of ejecting a fragment 
[02:34.20]of the martian surface 
[02:35.34]into an earth-intersecting 
[02:36.59]orbit is even less probable 
[02:38.25]than such an event on 
[02:39.29]the moon, in view of 
[02:40.50]the moon’s smaller size 
[02:41.89]and closer proximity 
[02:43.20]to earth. .
