[ti:长难句31~40]
[ar:sunny]
[al:]
[by:sunny]
[00:00.00]31. Studies by hargrave 
[00:02.79]and geen estimated natural 
[00:04.20]community grazing rates 
[00:05.59]by measuring feeding 
[00:06.68]rates of　individual 
[00:07.64]zooplankton species 
[00:08.93]in the　laboratory and 
[00:09.89]then computing community 
[00:11.18]grazing rates for field 
[00:12.65]conditions　using the 
[00:13.70]known population density 
[00:15.25]of grazers. 32. In the 
[00:18.50]periods　of peak zooplankton 
[00:19.90]abundance, that is, 
[00:21.56]in the late spring and 
[00:22.70]in the summer, haney 
[00:23.96]recorded maximum daily 
[00:25.40]community grazing rates, 
[00:27.06]for nutrient-poor lakes 
[00:28.36]and bog lakes, respectively, 
[00:30.56]of 6.6 percent and 114 
[00:33.26]percent of daily phytoplankton 
[00:35.01]production.  33. The 
[00:37.71]hydrologic cycle, a 
[00:39.17]major topic in this 
[00:40.36]science, is the complete 
[00:41.87]cycle of phenomena through 
[00:43.21]which water passes, 
[00:44.62]beginning as atmospheric 
[00:46.12]water vapor, passing 
[00:47.62]into liquid and solid 
[00:48.92]form as precipitation, 
[00:50.48]thence along and into 
[00:51.67]the ground surface, 
[00:52.93]and finally again returning 
[00:54.39]to the form of atmospheric 
[00:55.98]water vapor by means 
[00:57.23]of evaporation and transpiration.  
[00:59.84]34. Only when a system 
[01:02.43]possesses natural or 
[01:03.53]artificial boundaries 
[01:04.68]that associate the water 
[01:06.09]within it with the hydrologic 
[01:07.48]cycle may the entire 
[01:08.73]system properly be termed 
[01:10.29]hydrogeologic.  35. 
[01:13.39]The historian Frederick 
[01:14.59]J. Turner wrote in the 
[01:15.90]1890’s that the agrarian 
[01:17.65]discontent that had 
[01:18.65]been developing steadily 
[01:19.95]in the united states 
[01:20.95]since about 1870 had 
[01:22.56]been precipitated by 
[01:23.71]the closing of the internal 
[01:25.06]frontier - that is, 
[01:26.70]the depletion of available 
[01:28.06]new land needed for 
[01:29.06]further expansion of 
[01:30.15]the american farming 
[01:31.31]system.  36. In the 
[01:34.17]early 1950’s, historians 
[01:36.62]who studied preindustrial 
[01:37.96]europe（which we may 
[01:38.92]define here as europe 
[01:40.01]in the period from roughly 
[01:41.21]1300 to 1800） began, 
[01:44.06]for the first time in 
[01:45.03]large numbers, to nvestigate 
[01:46.92]more of the preindustrial 
[01:48.18]european population 
[01:49.53]than the 2 or 3 percent 
[01:50.78]who comprised the political 
[01:52.32]and social elite: the 
[01:53.68]kings, generals, judges, 
[01:55.98]nobles, bishops, and 
[01:57.84]local magnates who had 
[01:59.09]hitherto usually filled 
[02:00.23]history books. 37. Historians 
[02:04.28]such as le roy ladurie 
[02:05.64]have used the documents 
[02:06.84]to extract case histories, 
[02:08.70]which have illuminated 
[02:09.75]the attitudes of different 
[02:10.90]social groups （these 
[02:12.00]attitudes include, but 
[02:13.45]are not confined to, 
[02:14.79]attitudes toward crime 
[02:16.00]and　the law）and have 
[02:16.79]revealed how the authorities 
[02:18.25]administered justice. 
[02:20.11]38. It can be inferred 
[02:22.15]from the passage that 
[02:23.25]a historian who wished 
[02:24.40]to compare crime rates 
[02:25.56]per thousand in a european 
[02:26.96]city in one decade of 
[02:28.31]the fifteenth century 
[02:29.36]with crime rates in 
[02:30.36]another decade of that 
[02:31.61]century would probably 
[02:32.81]be most aided by better 
[02:34.21]information about which 
[02:35.46]of the following? 39. 
[02:38.46]My point is that its 
[02:39.51]central consciousness - 
[02:40.96]its profound understanding 
[02:42.37]of class and gender 
[02:43.57]as shaping influences 
[02:44.87]on people’s lives - 
[02:46.21]owes much to that earlier 
[02:47.57]literary heritage, a 
[02:48.87]heritage that, in general, 
[02:50.68]has not been sufficiently 
[02:51.98]valued by most contemporary 
[02:53.73]literary critics.  40. 
[02:56.73]Even the requirement 
[02:57.84]that biomaterials processed 
[02:59.59]from these materials 
[03:00.48]be nontoxic to host 
[03:01.79]tissue can be met by 
[03:03.00]techniques derived from 
[03:04.32]studying the reactions 
[03:05.64]of tissue cultures to 
[03:06.89]biomaterials or from 
[03:08.29]short-term implants...
