[ti:长难句41~50]
[ar:sunny]
[al:]
[by:sunny]
[00:00.00]121. Yet waizer’s argument, 
[00:03.57]however deficient, does 
[00:04.93]point to one of the 
[00:05.73]most serious weak-nesses 
[00:07.12]of capitalism-namely, 
[00:08.62]that it brings to predominant 
[00:10.01]positions in a society 
[00:11.40]people who, no matter 
[00:12.76]how legitimately they 
[00:13.84]have earned their material 
[00:14.90]rewards, often lack 
[00:16.39]those　other qualities 
[00:17.48]that evoke affection 
[00:18.54]or admiration.  122. 
[00:22.03]The appreciation of 
[00:23.03]traditional oral american 
[00:24.26]indian literature has 
[00:25.37]been limited, hampered 
[00:26.46]by poor translations 
[00:27.71]and by the difficulty, 
[00:29.04]even in the rare culturally 
[00:30.60]sensitive and aesthetically 
[00:32.00]satisfying translation, 
[00:33.64]of completely conveying 
[00:34.89]the original’s verse 
[00:35.82]structure, tone, and 
[00:37.32]syntax. 123. Mores, 
[00:41.37]which embodied each 
[00:42.31]culture’s ideal principles 
[00:43.95]for governing every 
[00:44.85]citizen, were developed 
[00:46.20]in the belief that the 
[00:47.04]foundation of a community 
[00:48.39]lies in the cultivation 
[00:49.73]of individual powers 
[00:50.84]to be placed in service 
[00:52.14]to the community.  124. 
[00:55.46]Only in the case of　
[00:56.57]the february revolution 
[00:57.85]do we lack　a useful 
[00:58.90]description of participants　　
[01:00.31]that might characterize 
[01:01.50]it in the light of what 
[01:02.50]social history has taught 
[01:03.76]us about the process 
[01:04.84]of revolutionary mobilization. 
[01:07.23]125. As a consequence, 
[01:10.48]it may prove difficult 
[01:11.62]or impossible to establish 
[01:13.28]for a successful revolution 
[01:14.76]a comprehensive and 
[01:15.71]trustworthy picture 
[01:16.81]of those who participated, 
[01:18.40]or to answer even the 
[01:19.40]most basic questions 
[01:20.53]one might pose concerning 
[01:21.79]the social origins of 
[01:22.89]the insurgents. 126. 
[01:26.48]Anthropologists and 
[01:27.57]others are on much firmer 
[01:28.92]ground when they attempt 
[01:30.01]to describe the cultural 
[01:31.46]norms for a small homogeneous 
[01:33.35]tribe or village than 
[01:34.56]when they undertake 
[01:35.40]the formidable task 
[01:36.39]of discovering the norms 
[01:37.45]that exist in a complex 
[01:38.89]modern nation state 
[01:40.03]composed of many disparate 
[01:41.64]groups. 127. The Italian 
[01:45.46]influence is likely, 
[01:46.90]whatever Valdez immediate 
[01:48.45]source: the Mexican 
[01:49.89]carpas themselves are 
[01:51.06]said to have originated 
[01:52.23]from the theater pieces 
[01:53.43]of a sixteenth-century 
[01:54.68]Spanish writer inspired 
[01:56.28]by encounters with Italian 
[01:57.87]commedia dell’arte troupes 
[01:59.28]on tour in Spain. 128. 
[02:02.95]It has thus generally 
[02:04.15]been by way of the emphasis 
[02:05.54]on oral literary creativity 
[02:07.35]that these Chicano writers, 
[02:09.00]whose English language 
[02:10.09]works are sometimes 
[02:11.23]uninspired, developed 
[02:12.68]the powerful and arresting 
[02:14.03]language that characterized 
[02:15.46]their spanish-language 
[02:16.62]works. 129. To measure 
[02:20.31]them properly, monitoring 
[02:21.90]equipment would have 
[02:22.79]to be laid out on a 
[02:23.70]grid at intervals of 
[02:24.68]at most 50 kilometers, 
[02:26.39]with sensors at each 
[02:27.43]grid point lowered deep 
[02:28.67]in the ocean and kept 
[02:29.67]there for many months. 
[02:31.56]130. This declaration，
[02:34.40]which was echoed in 
[02:35.51]the text of the Fourteenth 
[02:36.85]Amendment，was designed 
[02:38.40]primarily to counter 
[02:39.65]the Supreme Court’s 
[02:40.53]ruling in Dred Scott 
[02:41.64]v. Sandford that Black 
[02:43.73]people in the United 
[02:44.62]States could be denied 
[02:45.89]citizenship. 131. The 
[02:49.32]broad language of the 
[02:50.46]amendment strongly suggests 
[02:52.06]that its framers were 
[02:53.14]proposing to write into 
[02:54.45]the constitution not 
[02:55.59]a laundry list of specific 
[02:57.14]civil rights but a principle 
[02:58.48]of equal citizenship 
[02:59.62]that forbids organized 
[03:00.98]society from treating 
[03:02.23]any individual as a 
[03:03.26]member of an inferior 
[03:04.37]class. 132. This doctrine 
[03:08.35]has broadened the application 
[03:10.00]of the fourteenth amendment 
[03:11.45]to other, nonracial 
[03:12.73]forms of discrimination, 
[03:14.23]for while some justices 
[03:15.73]have refused to find, 
[03:17.07]any legislative　classification 
[03:18.96]other than race to be 
[03:19.96]constitutionally disfavored, 
[03:21.71]most have been receptive 
[03:22.85]to arguments that at 
[03:23.81]least some nonracial 
[03:24.95]discriminations. sexual 
[03:26.35]discrimination in particular, 
[03:28.18]are "suspect" and deserve 
[03:29.39]this heightened scrutiny 
[03:30.57]by the courts. 133. 
[03:34.23]Only when a system possesses 
[03:35.87]natural or artificial 
[03:36.92]boundaries that associate　
[03:38.40]the water within it 
[03:39.35]with the hydrologic 
[03:40.35]cycle may the entire 
[03:41.54]system properly be termed 
[03:43.15]hydrogeologic. 
