[ti:长难句81~90]
[ar:sunny]
[al:]
[by:sunny]
[00:00.00]81. Not only are liver 
[00:02.70]transplants never rejected, 
[00:04.48]but they even induce 
[00:05.42]a state of donor-specific 
[00:07.10]unresponsiveness in　
[00:08.26]which subsequent transplants 
[00:09.85]of other organs, such 
[00:11.50]as skin, from that donor 
[00:13.00]are accepted permanently.  
[00:15.04]82. As rock interface 
[00:17.73]are crossed, the elastic 
[00:19.48]characteristics encountered （
[00:20.76]by seismic waves）generally 
[00:22.51]change abruptly, which 
[00:23.96]causes part of the energy 
[00:25.40]to be reflected back 
[00:26.50]to the surface, where 
[00:27.65]it is recorded by seismic 
[00:29.23]instruments. 83. While 
[00:32.23]the new　doctrine seems 
[00:33.48]almost certainly correct, 
[00:35.09]the one papyrus fragment 
[00:36.67]raises the specter that 
[00:37.81]another may be unearthed, 
[00:39.21]showing, for instance, 
[00:40.85]that　it was a posthumous 
[00:42.04]production of the　danaid 
[00:43.20]tetralogy which bested 
[00:44.60]sophocles, and throwing 
[00:46.29]the date once more into 
[00:47.43]utter confusion. 84. 
[00:50.37]The methods that a community　
[00:51.67]devises to perpetuate 
[00:53.01]itself come into being 
[00:54.17]to preserve aspects 
[00:55.31]of the cultural legacy 
[00:56.65]that that community 
[00:57.45]perceives as essential. 
[00:59.50]85. Traditionally, pollination 
[01:02.59]by wind has been viewed 
[01:03.64]as a reproductive process 
[01:05.14]marked by random events 
[01:06.64]in which the vagaries 
[01:07.81]of the wind are compensated 
[01:09.26]for by the generation 
[01:10.46]of vast quantities of 
[01:11.65]pollen, so that the 
[01:12.85]ultimate production 
[01:13.85]of new seeds is assured 
[01:15.15]at the expense of producing 
[01:16.39]much more pollen than 
[01:17.54]is actually used.  86. 
[01:20.78]Because the potential 
[01:21.78]hazards pollen grains 
[01:23.14]are subject to as they 
[01:24.17]are transported over 
[01:25.21]long distances are enormous, 
[01:27.06]wind pollinated plants 
[01:28.31]have, in the view above, 
[01:30.10]compensated for the 
[01:31.20]ensuing loss of pollen 
[01:32.79]through happenstance 
[01:33.84]by virtue of producing 
[01:35.04]an amount of pollen 
[01:36.03]that is one to three 
[01:37.03]orders of magnitude 
[01:38.18]greater than the amount 
[01:39.17]produced by species 
[01:40.37]pollinated by insects.  
[01:42.46]87. For example, the 
[01:44.85]spiral arrangement of　
[01:46.06]scale-bract complexes 
[01:47.50]on ovule-bearing pine 
[01:48.70]cones, where the female 
[01:50.28]reproductive organs 
[01:51.54]of conifers are located, 
[01:53.18]is important to the 
[01:54.03]production of airflow 
[01:55.32]patterns that spiral 
[01:56.56]over the cone’s surfaces, 
[01:58.17]thereby passing airborne 
[01:59.60]pollen　from one scale 
[02:00.96]to the next. 88. Friedrich 
[02:04.20]Engels, however, predicted 
[02:06.09]that women would be 
[02:06.93]liberated from the “
[02:07.84]social, legal, and economic 
[02:09.98]subordination” of the 
[02:11.07]family by technological 
[02:12.67]developments that made 
[02:13.71]possible the recruitment 
[02:14.95]of “the whole female 
[02:15.96]sex into public industry”.  
[02:18.25]89. It was not the change 
[02:20.75]in office technology, 
[02:22.25]but rather the separation 
[02:23.39]of secretarial work, 
[02:24.73]previously seen as an 
[02:25.82]apprenticeship for beginning 
[02:27.07]managers, from administrative 
[02:28.92]work that in the 1880’s 
[02:30.56]created a new class 
[02:31.76]of "dead-end" jobs, 
[02:33.01]thenceforth considered "
[02:34.20]women’s work." 90. The 
[02:36.98]increase in the numbers 
[02:38.09]of married women employed 
[02:39.39]outside the home in 
[02:40.48]the twentieth century 
[02:41.53]had less to do with 
[02:42.53]the mechanization of 
[02:43.46]housework and an increase 
[02:44.87]in leisure time for 
[02:45.96]these women than it 
[02:46.81]did with their own economic 
[02:48.10]necessity and with high 
[02:49.31]marriage rates that 
[02:50.20]shrank the available 
[02:51.15]pool of single women 
[02:52.25]workers, previously, 
[02:53.93]in many cases, the only 
[02:55.68]women employers would 
[02:56.82]hire. 
