[ti:长难句11~20]
[ar:sunny]
[al:]
[by:sunny]
[00:00.00]21. As my own studies 
[00:02.50]have advanced, i have 
[00:03.71]been increasingly impressed 
[00:05.12]with the functional 
[00:05.92]similarities between 
[00:07.06]insect and vertebrate 
[00:08.17]societies and less so 
[00:09.46]with the structural 
[00:10.31]differences that seem, 
[00:11.65]at first glance, to 
[00:12.95]constitute such an immense 
[00:14.43]gulf between them. 22. 
[00:17.39]Although fiction assuredly 
[00:18.64]springs from political 
[00:19.87]circumstances, its authors 
[00:21.78]react to those circumstances 
[00:23.37]in ways other than ideological, 
[00:25.46]and talking about novels 
[00:26.81]and stories primarily 
[00:28.15]as instruments of ideology 
[00:29.79]circumvents much of 
[00:30.84]the fictional enterprise.  
[00:32.82]23. Is this a defect, 
[00:35.34]or are the authors working 
[00:36.71]out of, or trying to 
[00:37.92]forge, a different kind 
[00:39.42]of aesthetic?  24. In 
[00:42.31]addition, the style 
[00:43.56]of some black novels, 
[00:45.09]like jean toomer's cane, 
[00:46.75]verges on expressionism 
[00:48.23]or surrealism; does 
[00:50.12]this technique provide 
[00:51.28]a counterpoint to the 
[00:52.28]prevalent theme that 
[00:53.17]portrays the fate, against 
[00:54.81]which black heroes are 
[00:55.90]pitted, a theme usually 
[00:57.40]conveyed by more naturalistic 
[00:59.00]modes of expression? 
[01:00.90]25. Black fiction surveys 
[01:03.79]a wide variety of novels, 
[01:05.73]bringing to our attention 
[01:07.14]in the process some 
[01:08.17]fascinating and little-known 
[01:09.51]works like James Weldon 
[01:11.01]Johnson's Autobiography 
[01:12.46]of an Ex-Colored Man. 
[01:13.67]26. Although these molecules 
[01:16.50]allow radiation at visible 
[01:18.14]wavelengths, where most 
[01:19.64]of the energy of sunlight 
[01:20.93]is concentrated, to 
[01:22.28]pass through, they absorb 
[01:24.01]some of the longer-wavelength, 
[01:25.78]infrared emissions radiated 
[01:27.26]from the earth’s surface, 
[01:28.71]radiation that would 
[01:29.71]otherwise be transmitted 
[01:31.00]back into space. 27. 
[01:34.43]The role those anthropologists 
[01:36.14]ascribe to evolution 
[01:37.53]is not of dictating 
[01:38.57]the details of human 
[01:39.62]behavior but one of 
[01:40.67]imposing constraints - 
[01:42.21]ways of feeling, thinking, 
[01:44.01]and acting that "come 
[01:45.15]naturally" in archetypal 
[01:46.45]situations in any culture.  
[01:48.79]28. Which of the following 
[01:51.09]most probably provides 
[01:52.43]an appropriate analogy 
[01:53.73]from human morphology 
[01:54.98]for the "details" versus "
[01:56.17]constraints" distinction 
[01:57.37]made in the passage 
[01:58.37]in relation to human 
[01:59.56]behavior?  29. A low 
[02:02.65]number of algal cells 
[02:04.15]in the presence of a 
[02:05.04]high number of grazers 
[02:06.39]suggested, but did not 
[02:07.79]prove, that the grazers 
[02:09.39]had removed most of 
[02:10.39]the algae. 30. Perhaps 
[02:13.46]the fact many of these 
[02:14.56]first studies considered 
[02:15.87]only algae of a size 
[02:17.26]that could be collected 
[02:18.25]in a net (net phytoplankton), 
[02:20.10]a practice that overlooked 
[02:21.28]the smaller phytoplankton (
[02:22.84]nannoplankton) that 
[02:23.73]we now know grazers 
[02:25.04]are most likely to feed 
[02:26.17]on , led to a de-emphasis 
[02:28.03]of the role of grazers 
[02:29.17]in subsequent research. 
