[ti:长难句41~50]
[ar:sunny]
[al:]
[by:sunny]
[00:00.00]51. The best evidence 
[00:02.59]for the layered-mantle 
[00:03.64]thesis is the well-established 
[00:05.37]fact that volcanic rocks 
[00:06.89]found on oceanic islands, 
[00:08.64]islands believed to 
[00:09.64]result from mantle plumes 
[00:11.07]arising from the lower 
[00:12.29]mantle, are composed 
[00:13.64]of material fundamentally 
[00:14.89]different from that 
[00:15.59]of the mid-ocean ridge 
[00:16.65]system, whose source, 
[00:18.34]most　geologists contend, 
[00:20.18]is the upper mantle. 
[00:22.00]52. Some geologists, 
[00:24.79]however, on the basis 
[00:26.20]of observations concerning 
[00:27.65]mantle　xenoliths, argue 
[00:29.20]that the mantle is　not 
[00:30.45]layered, but that heterogeneity 
[00:32.25]is created by fluids 
[00:33.56]rich in "incompatible 
[00:34.61]elements" （elements 
[00:35.56]tending toward　liquid 
[00:36.65]rather than solid state）
[00:37.96]percolating upward and 
[00:39.17]transforming　portions 
[00:40.51]of the upper mantle　
[00:41.51]irregularly, according 
[00:43.01]to the vagaries of the 
[00:44.15]fluids’ pathways.  53. 
[00:47.51]Fallois proposed that 
[00:48.67]Proust had tried to 
[00:49.78]begin a novel in 1908, 
[00:51.81]abandoned it for what 
[00:52.78]was to be a long demonstration 
[00:54.37]of saint-beuve’s blindness 
[00:55.92]to the real nature of 
[00:56.92]great writing, found 
[00:58.28]the essay giving rise 
[00:59.43]to personal memories 
[01:00.53]and fictional developments, 
[01:02.12]and allowed these to 
[01:02.98]take over it a steadily 
[01:04.18]developing novel. 54. 
[01:07.32]The very richness and 
[01:08.59]complexity of the　meaningful 
[01:10.14]relationships that kept　
[01:11.39]presenting and rearranging 
[01:12.68]themselves　on all levels, 
[01:14.50]from abstract intelligence 
[01:15.98]to profound dreamy feelings, 
[01:18.00]made it difficult for 
[01:19.04]proust to set them out 
[01:20.29]coherently.  55. But 
[01:23.40]those of who hoped, 
[01:24.45]with kolb, that kolb’s 
[01:25.81]newly published complete 
[01:27.00]edition of Proust’s 
[01:28.04]correspondence for 1909 
[01:29.90]would document the process 
[01:31.25]in greater detail are 
[01:32.34]disappointed. 56. Now 
[01:35.61]we must also examine 
[01:36.96]the culture as we Mexican 
[01:38.31]Americans have experienced 
[01:39.76]it, passing from a sovereign 
[01:41.42]people to compatriots 
[01:42.51]with newly arriving 
[01:43.56]settlers to, finally 
[01:45.06]a conquered people a 
[01:46.03]charter minority on 
[01:47.17]our own land.  57. It 
[01:50.53]is possible to make 
[01:51.57]specific complementary 
[01:52.76]dna’s （cdna’s）that can 
[01:54.42]serve as molecular probes 
[01:56.12]to seek out the messenger 
[01:57.32]rna’s （mrna’s）of the 
[01:59.32]peptide hormones. If 
[02:01.42]brain cells are making 
[02:02.68]the hormones, the cells 
[02:04.03]will contain these mrnas. 
[02:06.53]if the products the 
[02:07.37]brain cells make resemble 
[02:08.68]the hormones but are 
[02:09.89]not identical to them, 
[02:11.43]then the cdna’s should 
[02:12.75]still bind to these 
[02:13.84]mrna’s, but should not 
[02:15.64]bind as tightly as they 
[02:16.79]would to mrna’s for 
[02:18.00]the true hormones. 58. 
[02:21.00]The molecular approach 
[02:22.04]to detecting peptide 
[02:23.25]hormones using cdna 
[02:24.90]probes should also be 
[02:26.15]much faster than the 
[02:27.25]immunological method 
[02:28.34]because it can take 
[02:29.25]years of tedious purifications 
[02:30.90]to isolate peptide hormones 
[02:32.67]and then develop antiserums 
[02:34.26]to them. 59. Nevertheless, 
[02:37.86]researchers of the pleistocene 
[02:39.46]epoch have developed 
[02:40.51]all sorts of more or 
[02:41.65]less fanciful model 
[02:42.86]schemes of how they 
[02:43.87]would have arranged 
[02:44.67]the ice age had they 
[02:45.71]been in charge of events.  
[02:47.67]60. This succession 
[02:49.76]was based primarily 
[02:51.06]on a series of deposits　
[02:52.51]and events not directly 
[02:53.78]related to glacial and 
[02:54.82]interglacial periods, 
[02:56.42]rather than on the more 
[02:57.39]usual modern method 
[02:58.53]of studying biological 
[02:59.93]remains found in interglacial 
[03:01.48]beds themselves interstratified 
[03:03.32]within glacial deposits. .
