[ti:长难句1~10]
[ar:sunny]
[al:]
[by:sunny]
[00:00.00]1. That sex ratio will 
[00:02.40]be favored which maximizes 
[00:04.01]the number of descendants 
[00:05.21]an individual will have 
[00:06.25]and　hence the number 
[00:07.04]of gene copies transmitted. 
[00:09.29]2. (this is) a desire 
[00:11.48]to throw over reality 
[00:12.84]a light that never was 
[00:13.82]might give away abruptly 
[00:15.07]to the desire on the 
[00:15.96]part of what we might 
[00:17.17]consider a novelist-scientist 
[00:18.92]to record exactly and 
[00:20.11]concretely the structure 
[00:21.36]and texture of a flower .  
[00:23.29]3. Hardy's weakness 
[00:25.54]derived from his apparent 
[00:26.89]inability to control 
[00:28.14]the comings and goings 
[00:29.28]of these divergent impulses 
[00:30.78]and from his unwillingness 
[00:32.03]to cultivate and sustain 
[00:33.32]the energetic and risky 
[00:34.62]ones. 4. Virginia Woolf's 
[00:37.86]provocative statement 
[00:39.20]about her intentions 
[00:40.29]in writing Mrs. Dalloway 
[00:41.70]has regularly been　ignored 
[00:43.14]by the critics, since 
[00:44.43]it highlights an aspect 
[00:45.78]of her literary interests 
[00:46.96]very different from 
[00:47.82]the traditional picture 
[00:48.86]of the "poetic" novelist 
[00:50.06]concerned with examining 
[00:51.31]states of reverie and 
[00:52.51]vision and with following 
[00:53.81]the intricate pathways 
[00:55.09]of individual consciousness.  
[00:57.20]5. As she put it in 
[00:59.28]the common reader, “
[01:00.37]it is safe to say that 
[01:01.53]not a single law has 
[01:02.57]been framed or one stone 
[01:04.07]set upon another because 
[01:05.32]of anything Chaucer 
[01:06.36]said or wrote; and yet, 
[01:08.45]as we read him, we are 
[01:09.76]absorbing morality at 
[01:10.90]every pore.”  6. With 
[01:13.73]the conclusion of a 
[01:14.57]burst activity , the 
[01:15.87]lactic acid level is 
[01:17.21]high in the body fluids , 
[01:18.82]leaving the large animal 
[01:20.14]vulnerable to attack 
[01:21.11]until the acid is reconverted , 
[01:23.01]via oxidative metabolism , 
[01:25.15]by the liver into glucose , 
[01:26.89]which is then sent (
[01:27.79]in part) back to the 
[01:28.70]muscles for glycogen 
[01:30.09]resynthesis .  7. Although 
[01:33.37]gutman admits that forced 
[01:34.78]separation by sale was 
[01:36.26]frequent, he shows that 
[01:37.61]the slaves’ preference, 
[01:38.96]revealed most clearly 
[01:40.25]on plantations where 
[01:41.36]sale was infrequent, 
[01:42.68]was very much for stable 
[01:44.04]monogamy. 8. Gutman 
[01:46.73]argues convincingly 
[01:47.87]that the stability of 
[01:48.89]the black family encouraged　
[01:50.32]the transmission of-and 
[01:51.28]so was crucial in sustaining-the 
[01:53.01]black heritage of folklore, 
[01:54.81]music, and religious 
[01:56.26]expression from one 
[01:57.36]generation to another, 
[01:58.79]a heritage that slaves 
[01:59.93]were continually fashioning 
[02:01.34]out of their african 
[02:02.14]and american experiences.  
[02:04.48]9. This preference for 
[02:06.46]exogamy, gutman suggests, 
[02:08.90]may have derived from　
[02:10.01]west african rules governing 
[02:11.65]marriage, which, though 
[02:13.25]they differed from one 
[02:14.15]tribal group to another, 
[02:15.65]all involved some kind 
[02:16.89]of prohibition against 
[02:18.09]unions with close kin.  
[02:20.14]10. His thesis works 
[02:22.28]relatively well when 
[02:23.32]applied to discrimination 
[02:24.65]against blacks in the 
[02:25.76]united states, but his 
[02:27.21]definition of racial 
[02:28.29]prejudice as "racially-based 
[02:29.84]negative prejudgments 
[02:31.00]against a group generally 
[02:32.34]accepted as a race in 
[02:33.64]any given region of 
[02:34.68]ethnic competition, " 
[02:36.03]can be interpreted as 
[02:37.21]also including hostility 
[02:38.82]toward such ethnic groups 
[02:40.21]as the chinese in california 
[02:41.76]and the jews　in medieval 
[02:42.92]europe.
