[ti:长难句41~50]
[ar:sunny]
[al:]
[by:sunny]
[00:00.00]41. But achieving necessary 
[00:02.86]matches in physical 
[00:04.00]properties across interfaces 
[00:05.81]between living and nonliving 
[00:07.20]matter requires knowledge 
[00:08.50]of which molecules control 
[00:10.11]the bonding of cells 
[00:11.15]to each other - an area 
[00:12.56]that we have not yet 
[00:13.71]explored thoroughly.  
[00:15.56]42. Islamic law is a 
[00:18.15]phenomenon so different 
[00:19.36]from all other forms 
[00:20.51]of law - notwithstanding, 
[00:22.36]of course, a　considerable 
[00:24.03]and inevitable number 
[00:25.06]of coincidences with 
[00:26.23]one or the other　of 
[00:27.17]them as far as subject 
[00:28.53]matter and positive 
[00:29.56]enactments are concerned - 
[00:31.07]that its study is indispensable 
[00:32.92]in order to　appreciate 
[00:34.12]adequately the full 
[00:35.14]range of　possible legal 
[00:36.57]phenomena.  43. （both 
[00:39.68]jewish law and canon 
[00:40.87]law are more uniform 
[00:42.14]than islamic law.）though 
[00:44.28]historically there is 
[00:45.37]a discernible break 
[00:46.48]between jewish law of 
[00:47.68]the sovereign state 
[00:48.64]of ancient israel and 
[00:49.95]of the diaspora （the 
[00:50.84]dispersion of jewish 
[00:51.95]people after the conquest 
[00:53.50]of israel）, the spirit 
[00:54.93]of the legal matter 
[00:56.03]in later parts of the 
[00:57.29]old testament is very 
[00:58.65]close to that of the 
[00:59.54]talmud, one of the primary 
[01:01.25]codifications of jewish 
[01:02.81]law in the diaspora.  
[01:04.75]44. Islam, on the other 
[01:07.45]hand, represented a 
[01:08.70]radical breakaway from 
[01:10.01]the arab paganism that 
[01:11.31]preceded it; islamic 
[01:13.21]law is the result of 
[01:14.40]an examination,　from 
[01:15.76]a religious angle, (
[01:16.90]examination)of legal 
[01:18.17]subject matter that 
[01:19.20]was far from uniform, 
[01:20.71]comprising as it did 
[01:21.87]the various components 
[01:23.01]of the laws of pre-islamic　
[01:24.37]arabia and numerous 
[01:25.42]legal elements　taken 
[01:26.62]over from the non-arab 
[01:27.82]peoples　of the conquered 
[01:29.03]territories. 45. One 
[01:32.32]such novel idea is　that (
[01:33.82]idea) of inserting into 
[01:34.98]the chromosomes of plants 
[01:36.39]discrete genes that 
[01:37.32]are not a part of the 
[01:38.32]plants’ natural constitution：
[01:40.32]specifically, the idea 
[01:42.14]of inserting into nonleguminous 
[01:43.68]plants the genes, if 
[01:45.18]they can be identified 
[01:46.59]and isolated, that fit 
[01:48.09]the leguminous plants 
[01:49.25]to be hosts for nitrogen-fixing 
[01:51.14]bacteria. Hence, (there 
[01:53.39]is) the intensified 
[01:54.48]research on legumes.  
[01:56.61]46. It is　one of nature’s 
[01:59.45]great ironies that the　
[02:00.65]availability of nitrogen 
[02:02.20]in the soil frequently 
[02:03.40]sets an upper limit 
[02:04.40]on plant growth even 
[02:05.59]though the plants’ leaves　
[02:06.70]are bathed in a sea 
[02:07.75]of nitrogen gas.  47. 
[02:11.11]Unless they succeed, 
[02:12.42]the　yield gains of the 
[02:13.51]green revolution will 
[02:14.56]be largely lost even 
[02:16.01]if the genes in　legumes 
[02:17.26]that equip those plants 
[02:18.36]to enter　into a symbiosis 
[02:19.96]with nitrogen fixers　
[02:21.17]are identified and isolated, 
[02:23.26]and even if　the transfer 
[02:24.46]of those gene complexes, 
[02:26.21]once they are found, 
[02:27.51]becomes possible.  48. 
[02:30.57]Its subject（to use maynard 
[02:32.03]mack’s categories）is　"
[02:33.28]life-as-spectacle, " 
[02:34.62]for readers, 　　diverted 
[02:35.93]by its various incidents, 
[02:37.53]observe its hero odysseus 
[02:39.07]primarily from without; 
[02:41.12]the tragic iliad, however, 
[02:43.23]presents "life-as-experience"：
[02:44.73]readers　are asked to 
[02:45.82]identify with the mind 
[02:47.09]of achilles, whose motivations 
[02:49.09]render him a not particularly 
[02:50.59]likable hero.  49. Most 
[02:54.07]striking among the many 
[02:55.25]asymmetries evident 
[02:56.50]in an adult flatfish 
[02:57.70]is eye placement: before 
[02:59.20]maturity one eye migrates, 
[03:01.15]so that in an adult 
[03:02.15]flatfish both eyes are 
[03:03.70]on the same side of 
[03:04.70]the head.  50. A critique 
[03:07.65]of Handlin’s interpretation 
[03:09.06]of why legal slavery 
[03:10.40]did not appear until 
[03:11.56]the 1660’s suggests 
[03:13.40]that assumptions about 
[03:14.40]the relation between 
[03:15.40]slavery and racial prejudice 
[03:17.06]should be reexamined, 
[03:18.31]and that explanations 
[03:19.46]for the different treatment 
[03:20.56]of black slaves in north 
[03:21.92]and South America should 
[03:23.17]be expanded. 
