[ti:长难句41~50]
[ar:sunny]
[al:]
[by:sunny]
[00:00.00]101. Wwith regard to 
[00:03.75]this last question, 
[00:05.00]we might note in passing 
[00:06.34]that thompson, while 
[00:07.59]rightly restoring laboring 
[00:09.04]people to the stage 
[00:09.93]of eighteen-century 
[00:11.07]english history, has 
[00:12.39]probably exaggerated 
[00:13.76]the opposition of these 
[00:14.92]people to the inroads 
[00:16.12]of capitalist consumerism 
[00:17.65]in general: for example, 
[00:19.40]laboring people in eighteen-century 
[00:21.25]england readily shifted 
[00:22.45]from home-brewed beer 
[00:23.34]to standardized beer 
[00:24.54]produced by huge, heavily 
[00:26.37]capitalized urban breweries. 
[00:28.82]102. The correlation 
[00:31.26]of carbon dioxide with 
[00:32.50]temperature, of course, 
[00:34.10]does not establish whether 
[00:35.50]changes in atmospheric 
[00:36.84]composition caused the 
[00:38.14]warming and cooling 
[00:39.09]trends or were caused 
[00:40.23]by their.  103. Such 
[00:43.57]philosophical concerns 
[00:44.92]as the mind-body problem 
[00:46.37]or, more generally, 
[00:47.92]the nature of human 
[00:48.85]knowledge they believe, 
[00:50.15]are basic human questions 
[00:51.60]whose tentative philosophical 
[00:53.09]solutions have served 
[00:54.35]as the necessary foundations 
[00:55.93]on which all other intellectual 
[00:57.48]speculation has rested.  
[00:59.71]104. The idea of an 
[01:02.42]autonomous discipline 
[01:03.51]called "philosophy, " 
[01:04.85]distinct from and sitting 
[01:06.01]in judgment on such 
[01:07.15]pursuits as theology 
[01:08.50]and science turns out, 
[01:09.95]on close examination, 
[01:11.48]to be of quite recent 
[01:12.57]origin.  105. They were 
[01:15.92]fighting, albeit discreetly, 
[01:18.01]to open the intellectual 
[01:19.21]world to the new science 
[01:20.35]and to liberate intellectual 
[01:21.75]life from ecclesiastical 
[01:23.26]philosophy and envisioned 
[01:24.75]their work as contributing 
[01:26.00]to the growth, not of 
[01:27.23]philosophy, but of research 
[01:28.98]in mathematics and physics. 
[01:31.12]106. But the recent 
[01:33.56]discovery of detailed 
[01:34.67]similarities in the 
[01:35.57]skeletal structure of 
[01:36.81]the flippers in all 
[01:37.70]three groups undermines 
[01:39.06]the attempt to explain 
[01:40.20]away superficial resemblance 
[01:41.79]as due to convergent 
[01:42.93]evolution - the independent 
[01:44.48]development of similarities 
[01:46.03]between unrelated groups 
[01:47.37]in response to similar 
[01:48.67]environmental pressures. 
[01:50.71]107. Human genes contain 
[01:53.65]too little information 
[01:54.75]even to specify which 
[01:56.14]hemisphere of the brain 
[01:57.34]each of a human’s 10’’ 
[01:58.53]neurons should occupy, 
[02:00.04]let alone the hundreds 
[02:01.28]of connections that 
[02:02.18]each neuron makes. 108. 
[02:05.71]For the woman who is 
[02:06.60]a practitioner of feminist 
[02:07.92]literary criticism, 
[02:09.29]the subjectivity versus 
[02:10.75]objectivity, or critic-as-artist-or-
[02:13.04]scientist, debate has 
[02:14.59]special significance; 
[02:16.54]for her, the question 
[02:17.82]is not only academic, 
[02:19.53]but political as well, 
[02:20.96]and her definition will 
[02:22.01]court special risks 
[02:22.96]whichever side of the 
[02:24.10]issue it favors. 109. 
[02:27.59]If she defines feminist 
[02:29.04]criticism as objective 
[02:30.54]and scientific - a valid, 
[02:32.39]verifiable, intellectual 
[02:34.03]method that anyone, 
[02:35.21]whether man or woman , 
[02:36.78]can perform - the definition 
[02:38.40]not only precludes the 
[02:39.56]critic-as-artist approach, 
[02:41.26]but may also impede 
[02:42.45]accomplishment of the 
[02:43.39]utilitarian political 
[02:44.75]objectives of those 
[02:45.84]who seek to change the 
[02:46.82]academic establishment 
[02:48.34]and its thinking, especially 
[02:50.03]about sex roles. 110. 
[02:53.51]These questions are 
[02:54.46]political in the sense 
[02:55.51]that the debate over 
[02:56.40]them will inevitably 
[02:57.40]be less an exploration 
[02:58.76]of abstract matters 
[02:59.89]in a spirit of disinterested 
[03:01.39]inquiry than an academic 
[03:02.84]power struggle in which 
[03:04.09]the careers and professional 
[03:05.43]fortunes of many women 
[03:06.82]scholars-only now entering 
[03:08.42]the academic profession 
[03:09.76]in substantial numbers-will 
[03:11.21]be at stake, and with 
[03:12.51]them the chances for 
[03:13.54]a distinctive contribution 
[03:15.00]to humanistic understanding, 
[03:16.84]a contribution that 
[03:17.93]might be an important 
[03:19.04]influence against sexism 
[03:20.43]in our society. 
