[ti:长难句41~50]
[ar:sunny]
[al:]
[by:sunny]
[00:00.00]91. For one thing, no 
[00:02.75]population can be driven 
[00:04.29]entirely by density-independent 
[00:06.28]factors all the time.  
[00:08.43]92. In order to understand 
[00:11.03]the nature of the ecologist’s 
[00:12.62]investigation, we may 
[00:14.11]think of the density-dependent 
[00:15.61]effects on growth parameters 
[00:17.25]as the "signal" ecologists 
[00:18.70]are trying to isolate 
[00:19.89]and interpret, one that 
[00:21.23]tends to make the population 
[00:22.82]increase from relatively 
[00:24.18]low values or decrease 
[00:25.78]from relatively high 
[00:26.92]ones, while the density-independent 
[00:29.06]effects act to produce "
[00:30.42]noise" in the population 
[00:31.71]dynamics. 93. But the 
[00:35.00]play’s complex view 
[00:36.29]of black self-esteem 
[00:37.50]and human solidarity 
[00:38.73]as compatible is no 
[00:39.84]more "contradictory" 
[00:40.87]than du bois’ famous, 
[00:42.17]well-considered ideal 
[00:43.42]of ethnic self-awareness 
[00:44.76]coexisting with human 
[00:46.01]unity, or fanon’s emphasis 
[00:47.95]on an ideal internationalism 
[00:49.59]that also accommodates 
[00:51.11]national identities 
[00:52.18]and roles.  94. In which 
[00:55.43]of the following does 
[00:56.43]the author of the passage 
[00:57.57]reinforce his criticism 
[00:59.12]of responses such as 
[01:00.26]isaacs’ to raisin in 
[01:01.56]the sun？  95. Iinheritors 
[01:05.04]of some of the　viewpoints 
[01:06.20]of early twentieth-century 
[01:07.54]progressive historians 
[01:08.75]such as beard and becker, 
[01:10.32]these recent historians 
[01:11.67]have put forward arguments 
[01:13.03]that deserve evaluation. 
[01:15.21]96. Despite these vague 
[01:17.81]categories, one should 
[01:19.36]not claim unequivocally 
[01:20.70]that hostility between 
[01:22.00]recognizable classes 
[01:23.34]cannot be legitimately 
[01:24.53]observed.  97. Yet those 
[01:27.78]who stress the achievement 
[01:28.98]of a general consensus 
[01:30.31]among the colonists 
[01:31.21]cannot fully understand 
[01:32.46]that consensus without 
[01:33.56]understanding the conflicts 
[01:35.06]that had to be overcome 
[01:36.36]or repressed in order 
[01:37.50]to reach it.  98. It 
[01:40.18]can be inferred from 
[01:41.03]the passage that the 
[01:42.00]author would be most 
[01:42.98]likely to agree with 
[01:43.98]which of the following 
[01:45.12]statements regarding 
[01:46.21]socioeconomic class 
[01:47.71]and support for the 
[01:48.62]rebel and loyalist causes 
[01:50.15]during the american 
[01:51.11]revolutionary war？  
[01:52.86]99. She wished to discard 
[01:55.48]the traditional methods 
[01:56.59]and established vocabularies 
[01:58.28]of such dance forms 
[01:59.42]as ballet and to explore 
[02:00.87]the internal sources 
[02:01.96]of human expressiveness.  
[02:03.96]100. Although it has 
[02:06.01]been possible to infer 
[02:07.20]from the goods and services 
[02:08.45]actually produced what 
[02:09.65]manufactures and servicing 
[02:11.20]trades thought their 
[02:11.98]customers wanted, only 
[02:13.68]a study of relevant 
[02:14.78]personal documents written 
[02:16.03]by actual consumers 
[02:17.28]will provide a precise 
[02:18.42]picture of who wanted 
[02:19.32]what. 
