[ti:长难句41~50]
[ar:sunny]
[al:]
[by:sunny]
[00:00.00]111. Perhaps he believed 
[00:02.84]that he could not criticize 
[00:04.28]American foreign policy 
[00:05.57]without endangering 
[00:06.67]the support for civil 
[00:07.76]rights that he had won 
[00:08.87]from the federal government.  
[00:10.85]112. However, some broods 
[00:14.00]possess a few snails 
[00:19.37]of the opposing hand, 
[00:20.65]and in predominantly 
[00:21.75]sinistral broods, the 
[00:23.20]incidence of dextrality 
[00:24.68]is surprisingly high.  
[00:26.73]113. In experiments, 
[00:29.82]an injection of cytoplasm 
[00:31.46]from dextral eggs changes 
[00:32.96]the pattern of sinistral 
[00:34.15]eggs, but an injection 
[00:35.75]from sinistral eggs 
[00:36.84]does not influence dextral 
[00:38.54]eggs.  114. Recently 
[00:42.17]some scientists have 
[00:43.18]concluded that meteorites 
[00:44.57]found on earth and long 
[00:45.82]believed to have a Martian 
[00:47.01]origin might actually 
[00:48.31]have been blasted free 
[00:49.46]of mars’s gravity by 
[00:50.65]the impact on mars of 
[00:51.95]other meteorites. 115. 
[00:55.75]Under the force of this 
[00:56.68]view, it was perhaps 
[00:58.12]inevitable that the 
[00:59.03]art of rhetoric should 
[00:59.96]pass from the status 
[01:01.12]of being regarded as 
[01:02.17]of questionable worth （
[01:03.26]because although it 
[01:04.26]might be both a source 
[01:05.51]of pleasure and a means 
[01:06.60]to urge people to right 
[01:07.95]action, it might also 
[01:09.64]be a means to distort 
[01:10.89]truth and a source of 
[01:11.98]misguided action）to 
[01:13.28]the status of being 
[01:14.23]wholly condemned.  116. 
[01:17.71]None of these translations 
[01:19.10]to screen and stage, 
[01:20.56]however, dramatize the 
[01:22.09]anarchy at the　conclusion 
[01:23.39]of a connecticut yankee, 
[01:24.84]which ends with the 
[01:25.70]violent overthrow　of 
[01:26.84]morgan’s three-year-old 
[01:28.09]progressive order and 
[01:29.18]his return to the nineteenth 
[01:30.53]century, where he apparently 
[01:32.23]commits suicide after 
[01:33.62]being labeled a lunatic 
[01:34.81]for his incoherent babblings 
[01:36.35]about drawbridges and 
[01:37.51]battlements.  117. Calculations 
[01:41.78]of the density of alloys 
[01:43.23]based on bernal-type 
[01:44.34]models of the alloys 
[01:45.53]metal component agreed 
[01:46.78]fairly well with the 
[01:47.87]experimentally determined 
[01:49.12]values from measurements 
[01:50.46]on alloys consisting 
[01:51.76]of a noble metal together 
[01:53.01]with a metalloid, such 
[01:54.40]as alloys of palladium 
[01:55.65]and silicon, or alloys 
[01:57.10]consisting of iron, 
[01:58.50]phosphorus, and carbon, 
[02:00.25]although small discrepancies 
[02:01.87]remained. 118. And walzer 
[02:05.62]advocates as the means 
[02:06.85]of eliminating this 
[02:07.76]tyranny and of restoring 
[02:09.31]genuine equality “the 
[02:10.45]abolition of the power 
[02:11.56]of money outside its 
[02:12.65]sphere”.  119. It is 
[02:16.14]now established that 
[02:17.28]the Milky Way is far 
[02:18.48]more extended and of 
[02:19.48]much greater mass than 
[02:20.67]was hitherto thought.  
[02:22.56]120. Is it not tyrannical, 
[02:25.81]in pascal’s sense, to 
[02:27.34]insist that those who 
[02:28.29]excel in “sensitivity” 
[02:29.59]or “the ability to express 
[02:31.04]compassion” merit equal 
[02:32.39]wealth with those who 
[02:33.28]excel in qualities (
[02:34.28]such as “the capacity 
[02:35.53]for hard work”) essential 
[02:36.82]in producing wealth? 
