[ti:长难句41~50]
[ar:sunny]
[al:]
[by:sunny]
[00:00.00]61. There have been 
[00:02.10]attempts to explain 
[00:03.17]these taboos in terms 
[00:04.31]of inappropriate social 
[00:05.51]relationships either 
[00:06.57]between those who are 
[00:07.57]involved and those who 
[00:08.81]are not simultaneously 
[00:10.21]involved in the satisfaction 
[00:11.87]of a bodily need, or 
[00:13.23]between those already 
[00:14.37]satiated and those who 
[00:15.62]appear to be shamelessly 
[00:16.92]gorging.  62. Many critics 
[00:20.43]of amily bronte’s novel 
[00:21.98]wuthering heights see 
[00:23.07]its second　part as a 
[00:24.23]counterpoint that comments 
[00:25.64]on, if it does not reverse, 
[00:27.68]the first part, where 
[00:28.84]a "romantic" reading 
[00:29.78]receives more confirmation.  
[00:32.04]63. Granted that the 
[00:34.28]presence of these elements 
[00:35.68]need not argue an　authorial 
[00:37.40]awareness of novelistic　
[00:38.65]construction comparable 
[00:39.85]to that of henry james, 
[00:41.40]their presence does 
[00:42.39]encourage attempts to 
[00:43.39]unify the novel’s　heterogeneous 
[00:45.35]parts. 64. This is not 
[00:48.90]because such an interpretation 
[00:50.51]necessarily stiffens 
[00:51.81]into a thesis（although 
[00:53.10]rigidity in any interpretation 
[00:54.90]of this or of any novel 
[00:56.25]is always a　danger）, 
[00:57.60]but because wuthering 
[00:58.51]heights has recalcitrant 
[00:59.71]elements of undeniable 
[01:01.12]power that, ultimately, 
[01:02.85]resist inclusion in 
[01:04.01]an all-encompassing　
[01:05.17]interpretation. 65. 
[01:08.35]The isotopic composition 
[01:09.96]of lead often varies 
[01:11.07]from one source of common 
[01:12.23]copper ore to another, 
[01:13.78]with variations exceeding 
[01:15.12]the measurement error; 
[01:16.78]and preliminary studies 
[01:18.03]indicate virtually uniform 
[01:19.48]isotopic composition 
[01:20.87]of the lead from a single 
[01:22.07]copper-ore source.  
[01:23.89]66. More probable is 
[01:26.32]bird transport, either 
[01:27.73]externally, by accidental 
[01:29.48]attachment of the seeds 
[01:30.78]to feathers, or internally, 
[01:32.64]by the swallowing of 
[01:33.68]fruit and subsequent　
[01:34.75]excretion of the seeds.  
[01:36.95]67. A long-held view 
[01:39.39]of the history of English 
[01:40.45]colonies that became 
[01:41.54]the United States has 
[01:42.75]been that England’s 
[01:43.45]policy toward these 
[01:44.68]colonies before 1763 
[01:46.90]was dictated by commercial 
[01:48.35]interests and that a 
[01:49.29]change to a more imperial 
[01:50.70]policy, dominated by 
[01:52.31]expansionist militarist 
[01:53.76]objectives, generated 
[01:55.25]the tensions that ultimately 
[01:56.62]led to the American 
[01:57.56]Revolution.  68. It 
[01:59.81]is not known how rare 
[02:01.12]this resemblance is, 
[02:02.46]or whether it is most 
[02:03.60]often seen in inclusions 
[02:05.10]of silicates such as 
[02:06.35]garnet, whose crystallography 
[02:08.17]is generally somewhat 
[02:09.26]similar to that of diamond; 
[02:11.46]but when present, the 
[02:12.67]resemblance is regarded 
[02:14.07]as compelling evidence 
[02:15.21]that the diamonds and 
[02:16.21]inclusions are truly 
[02:17.32]cogenetic. 69. Even 
[02:20.57]the "radical" critiques 
[02:21.68]of this mainstream research 
[02:23.18]model, such as the critique 
[02:24.98]developed in divided 
[02:26.23]society, attach the 
[02:27.78]issue of ethnic assimilation 
[02:29.34]too mechanically to 
[02:30.28]factors of economic 
[02:31.59]and social mobility 
[02:32.75]and are thus unable 
[02:33.70]to illuminate the cultural 
[02:35.00]subordination of puerto 
[02:36.29]ricans as a colonial 
[02:37.39]minority. 70. They are 
[02:40.29]called virtual particles 
[02:41.68]in order to distinguish 
[02:42.79]them from real particles，
[02:44.26]whose lifetimes are 
[02:45.40]not constrained　in the 
[02:46.45]same way，and which can 
[02:48.04]be detected.  .
